AJAY DHAGE

Web Developer/ Designer, **UI-UX**

PERSONAL PROFILE

Solution-driven Web Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript. Built products for desktop and mobile app users over 2+ years, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, thirdparty integrations and databases.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Designer/Developer, UI-UX

Simplotel Bengaluru Nov 2020 - present

- Gathered specifications and other key details to meet requirements of site development.
- · Conceptualized, planned and executed original designs for wide range of website properties.
- Delivered services as web developer, designer, application specialist and webmaster, acting as project manager for platform transition.
- Created software with computer scripting input and processed by software to generate commands, events, objects and characters for player interaction.
- Produced sample sites and received feedback about draft sites.
- Built user interface, data visualizations and designed overall user experience, resulting in 70% increase in sales.
- Promoted brand identity by creating company logos and delivering attractive, user-friendly and unique website.
- Designed user interface to meet client specifications and content management system.
- Enhanced functionality and appearance of website and repaired functionality issues.

Operations Executive

Unschool Bidar | July 2020- Oct 2020

- Built and strengthened relationships across functional leadership areas to keep revenue development and operational plans interconnected and effective.
- Devised, deployed and monitored processes to boost long-term business success and increase profit levels 60%.
- Managed cross-functional collaboration to drive team engagement and keep members on course to achieve demanding company targets.



CONTACT ME AT



Address

Post Warwatti B Tq Bhalki Dist Bidar, 585401



Phone

+917847019704



Email & Website

dhageajay008@gmail.com www.ajaydhage.in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ajay-dhage-88aab9164

SKILLS SUMMARY

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

ANGULAR

REACT, VUE.JS

PYTHON, DJANGO, FLASK

C,C++, JAVA

FRONT END DEVELOPEMENT

AWARDS RECEIVED



Elected as Vice Chairperson for College Fest called "Ebuzz" in 2019



Received National Level Code Hackathon Certificate from PDA, Gulbarga



Completed Internship at Intel FICE, Intel.

Internship at Intel FICE

Intel FICE, Bangalore | Mar 2019 - May 2019

- Worked on Intel Edison Kit learnt python programming, machine learning and worked on Ubuntu OS.
- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.
- Led projects and analyzed data to identify opportunities for improvement.
- Used coordination and planning skills to achieve results according to schedule.
- Exceeded goals through effective task prioritization and great work ethic.

Internshala Student Partner

Internshala | Dec 2019 to Mar 2020

- I worked at Internshala as Brand Ambassador of Internshala in my College . I was appointed by Samay Bhatnagar from Internshala, mail : isphiring@internshala.com.
- Resolved problems, improved operations and provided exceptional service.
- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.

Won National Level Code Hackathon

PDA College, Gulbarga | Jun 2019 - Sep 2019

- We won among top 10 in National Level Code Hackathon held at PDA, Gulbarga.
- Our project was "Overdose Detection and Monitoring ".
 We used NodeMCU, heart rate sensor, arduino, led lights, thinkspeak server and database.
- Participated in continuous improvement by generating suggestions, engaging in problem-solving activities to support teamwork.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.

Mega Al Project

Al Enabled Web Camera | Feb 2019 to May 2020

- Used latest machine learning concepts and algorithms to detect AI supervision.
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere.
- Completed all paperwork, recognizing any discrepancies and addressing them in a timely fashion.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Bachelor of Engineering Electronics & Communication Engineering

Guru Nanak Dev Engineering College Mar 2016 to Aug 2020

- Member of GRIN Publising Commitee
- Elected to Vice Chairperson for College Fest called " Ebuzz" in 2019
- Received National Level Code Hackathon Certificate from PDA, Gilbarga
- Final Year Research Project: Overdose Detection and Monitoring, Won in National Level Code Hackathon for awesome concept and implementation
- Completed Internship at Intel FICE, Intel.

Pre University College

Shaheen Independent PU College Bidar | Mar 2014 to April 2016

I secured 80% in my PUC

School

Sri Siddharoodh Public School Bidar | Mar 2004 to April 2014

 I secured 10 CGPA in my school, I was my school topper.

Certifications

Online Platforms | Mar 2016 to Aug 2020

- Member of GRIN Publising Committee
- Elected to Vice Chairperson for College Fest called " Ebuzz" in 2019
- Electronics C C++ Python from Sololearn
- Javascipt HTML CSS
- Android App Development
- Robotic Process Automation
- Won National Level Code Hackathon at PDA
- Brand Ambassador of Internshala at
- IESA Delegate Member (05/2019 07/2019)
- IETE Member (03/2019 Present)
- GRIN Publishing Author (06/2019 Present)
- Android App Development
- Frontend Fundamentals Using HTML,CSS,Javascipt and CSS
- UI/UX Design by Amazon UX Designer

Languages Known and Hobbies

English, Hindi, Kannada, Marathi.

My hobbies are solving rubik cube, web surfing.

ONLINE PRESENCE

You can visit my github profile, linkedin and other social media links to see my work.

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/ajay-dhage-88aab9164

 $\textbf{Github - } \underline{\text{https://github.com/githubajaydhage}}$

Website - www.ajaydhage.in

Whatsapp - +917847019704